GED ALEXANDER

07480138404 ged_a@aol.com

20 Bray Road Fulford, York YO10 4JG

Profile

I am an experienced, driven candidate who has had unique life experiences. I add value to any organisation given my wealth of experience in diverse roles over the years. I understand the human element of business and have military experience in management and critical thinking. I pride myself on being clam under pressure and capable of problem solving in difficult situations. I am charismatic and have a sense of humour. I believe in my abilities and have proven that I am capable of achieving results in most fields.

Experience

SHELA Limited - Founder - Present Recruitment APP/Platform startup.

British Army - Army Welfare Worker — 2016 - Present

I transferred to the Army Welfare Service after serving 10 years as an Army Chef. I had a successful career as a chef and wanted to learn new skills to add to my portfolio and professional development. (UK)

British Army - Army Chef - 2006 - 2016

I joined the British Army in June 2006 beginning my career as an Army Chef. During initial soldier training I was awarded the Soldiers medal and best recruit. I was promoted to the rank of Sgt within 81/2 years. (Germany)

Freight Services and Distributors Ltd - Manager - 2002-2004
I held the position of manager of this freight company, We held a subsidiary department engaging in the acquisition of products and distributing them throughout the Island (St. Lucia).

CIMPEX - Marketing and Advertising - 1998-2001

I began working with this company as a graphic designer after winning a logo competition to design a logo for the company. I was promoted to the marketing department after contributing positively to a marketing campaign which proved very successful (St. Lucia).

Optimum Printers — Graphic Designer -1996 - 1998

I was self taught graphic design and landed my first job as a graphic designer in a local printery. I quickly become the main graphic designer winning 2 logo competitions while employed at the company (St. Lucia).

Education

First Year of Study - LAW - Open University 2014-Present
CMI Level 4 Diploma in Management and Leadership - CMI - (2016)
Level 3 Certificate in Assessing Vocational Achievement - City & Guilds (2016)

Level 3 Award in Education and Training - Defence Awarding Organisation (2015)

NVQ Level 3 in Hospitality Supervision (2011)

Level 2 NVQ in Hospitality - Professional Cookery (2008)

Level 1 Coach - Basketball England

Skills

Instructing

Graphic Design

Chef

Business Development

References

Esther Louisy BA Special Education - 07805441224

6